# Tom Zhu

A self-starting, Computer Science student with professional experience who enjoys creating full-stack applications and solving problems. Can learn independently and has experience under pressure and in collaborative situations.

github.com/zhu-tom | linkedin.com/zhu-tom | www.zhutom.com

19 Redcar Crescent Kanata, ON K2K 3E2 (613) 762 - 3313 zhutom01@gmail.com

## **PROJECTS**

## **Carleton Timetable Creator** — *Python, Javascript*

Creates all possible timetable combinations for desired courses and time preferences. Displays in tabular format with CRN, time, location, professor, ratemyprofessor rating.

## **Fast Food Haven** — *Python, Javascript*

Shows web scraped coupons for fast food deals. Search and filtering functionality. Displays coupon expiry, location and distance of nearest franchise, and links to exact coupon.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Hot Glue Games**, Katimavik — *Quality Assurance Analyst*

JULY 2018 - AUGUST 2018

- Used attentive and analytical skills to discover bugs and issues
- Interacted and communicated with others using clear and concise bug reports
- Comfortable with a fast paced work environment with short deadlines

### **City of Ottawa**, Kanata — Camp Counselor

JULY 2017 - AUGUST 2017

- Supervised children to maintain a pleasant and safe environment for all campers
- · Led children through drills and activities

## Ottawa Fusion Volleyball Club — Athlete

**SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2019** 

- Exercised a strong work-ethic, punctuality, dedication
- Balanced commitment with school while maintaining a 93% grade average
- Experienced high pressure in collaborative environment

# **Athletics Council**, West Carleton — *Member*

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2019

- Refereed for school organized athletic events
- Organized Tournament of Champions, Athletic Banquet, Spirit Weeks

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Carleton University**, 12.0 GPA — Computer Science Honours (BCS)

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

• Started Carleton Volleyball Club (Vice President)

#### **SKILLS**

Dedication

Attention to Detail

**Initiative** 

**Critical Thinking** 

**Problem Solving** 

Collaboration

Adaptability

Listening

Independence

#### **AWARDS**

CuHacking 2020 Winner - Best use of UI Path

Dean's Honour List Fall 2019

OCDSB Silver Medal

#### **TECHNICAL**

**Python** 

Java

JavaScript

SQL

PHP